The news if finally worth reporting.
Dixie Times is a drama film directed by Sherrie Peterson.
A moonshiner turned sheriff's deputy helps bring in
the bad guys armed with duct tape.
The local newspaper reporter now has some major events to write about, and a sleepy
little Alabama farming community is making the news all over Dixie.
Briscoe Tanner, played by Ken R. Wheeler.
Alice Bentley, played by Stacey Turner.
Michael Bradley, played by Chad Fishburne.
Clifford Scruggs, played by Dan Mengini.
Horace Shaw, played by Justin Welborn.
Louis, played by Chris Burns.
Because of Winn-Dixie is a 2005 American comedy-drama film based on Kate DiCamillo's 2000 novel of the same name,
with the screenplay written by Joan Singleton, produced by Trevor Albert and directed by Wayne Wang.
The film was produced by Walden Media and released by 20th Century Fox.
Because of Winn-Dixie stars Jeff Daniels, Cicely Tyson, Eva Marie Saint,
Dave Matthews and AnnaSophia Robb in her feature film debut.
It premiered at the USA Film Festival on January 26, 2005, and
was theatrically released on February 18, 2005.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and earned $33.5
million against a production budget of $14 million.
It was released on DVD and VHS on August 9, 2005 by
20th Century Fox Home Entertainment.